Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Where is your son now?
Bringing in the other flock.
He'll be back soon.
Then send him for my father?
Then feed him supper.
Then he sleeps.
Then send him for your father.
Maybe we bury them.
Bury them deep.
By the creek where
the ground is soft.
Hole won't look fresh then.
Yeah.
Issaxche Rainwater?
That is me.
Your granddaughter
is Teonna Rainwater.
enrolled at the U.S. school
for Native Americans?
Yes?
I have a warrant
for her arrest.
Please step aside.
You say she is murdered?
I say she did the murders.
She killed two teachers
at the school. Now step aside.
My granddaughter?
You make no sense.
Why-why are you here?
What are you doing?
I saw a barn out back.
Check it. Check the teepee.
Harboring a fugitive
is a felony.
What is a fugitive?
Get out of my house now!
Ain't no sign of her in the...
What happened here?
She attacked me.
I pushed her back.
She must have hit her head
on the stove.
Why are you asking?
You were here. you saw everything.
Didn't you.
Yeah.
Yeah. she attacked you.
Let's keep looking.
Alex!
I'm coming!
Spencer!
Come on.
Catch your breath.
How well do you swim?
Under normal circumstances.
I would say quite well.
Hang on.
- Hang on to these. okay?
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah. Yeah.
What happened?
Ghost ship hit us.
How long can this stay afloat?
I don't know.
Doesn't really matter.
We're not gonna make through
the day without water or shade.
Hey. I gotta go back down.
What for?
We need things.
Hey. stay here.
That was a dumb thing to say.
Just stay in the
center of the hull.
Don't go towards the edge.
I'll stay in the center.
- Be right back.
- You'd better.
Alex!
Spencer!
We're drifting away from it!
We swim right now or we die.
Okay?
Come on!
Keep going!
Swim as hard as you can!
There you go! Keep going!
Come on!
This way. Come on. Come on.
Not your sharpest moment.
I'm aware. thank you.
This is not how
I thought I'd die.
Because it isn't.
Look at me.
This is hopeless.
Is it hopeless?
I'll admit we're gonna
need a little bit of luck.
We're certainly due some.
May not feel like it now...
but sitting on this hull
is about the luckiest thing
that ever happened to you.
I made contact with a ship
before we went down.
They know we're here. okay?
Wanna hope for something?
Hope they're coming. Okay?
Try and get all of
yourself underneath.
What about you?
I'm gonna work on my tan.
I'll catch up.
Good to see you moving.
Glad someone enjoys
seeing me moving.
I sure don't.
Pretty stiff?
Damn bed sucked all
my strength from me.
You were in it a while.
Might sleep standing
up from now on.
Well. if you figure out that
trick. gotta teach it to me.
Spencer's coming home.
From where?
Cara sent the last
letter to Africa.
That sounds like a long trip.
Six. eight weeks on a ship.
Another week on the train.
Then we get after their asses.
Start asking around real quiet
about who wants to
be on the posse.
Half the cowboys around
here went to California.
Quitters went to California.
Tough ones are still here.
Find some.
Want me to saddle you a horse?
No. I think
I'll just walk for today.
Make sure I don't
come unstitched.
Have a seat. Spur.
Are you currently employed?
Ma'am?
Do you have a job?
In the spring I have a job.
When the snow melts.
What ranch?
Ma'am. why are you so curious
about where I work?
Well. you're applying for the
position of Livestock Agent.
It would stand to
reason we consider
your previous employment
while making a decision.
Who's conducting
this interview?
I am.
What the hell does a woman
know about law enforcement?
Absolutely nothing.
But I know men.
You see. I can look in
a man's eye and know
if he can be trusted. if he
can maintain his composure
while facing adversity.
An element of this interview
you seem to be failing.
My own mama never
talked to me like that.
Mm. Maybe she should've.
Ain't a fucking woman
on this--
I'm afraid you lack
the temperament
this job requires.
We thank you for your interest.
And don't forget your hat.
Go easy on the head busting.
Nobody speaks
to my aunt like that.
We've been at it all morning.
And we've only found two.
It's a dangerous job
that don't pay well.
We're gonna have to sort through
a lot of drifters and bullies
to find true believers. ma'am.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you. sir.
So. are you
currently employed?
No. ma'am.
I have a homestead north
of Big Timber.
That's a long ride
from Big Timber.
Three days or more.
But three hours by train.
Them engines shrink
the world. aye?
For better or for worse.
I think worse in the long run.
You may be right.
We should mark
the calendar. ma'am.
It's rare when that happens.
I've seen you before.
At the Civic Center.
I don't miss a meeting.
McDowell: What makes you want to
be a Livestock Agent?
Well. if you think the
thieving's bad here. go east.
Go where there's
no cities at all
and a straight shot
to Sheridan...
No big ranches my way.
If we lose ten head. we feel it.
We lose twenty
and we're out of business.
Plus. I know the life.
Was a copper during the war.
when the stockyards was booming.
Half the city drunk.
trying to beat and
steal from the other half.
Why'd you quit?
The smell.
Fifteen million cattle
and three million people
all belching and pissing
and screaming and fighting.
crammed together
in the same place.
My apologies. ma'am. but there's
no gentle way to describe it.
I don't know what hell is but
it ain't worse than Chicago.
Now I try to limit the time
my feet spend on concrete.
Well. thank you for your
interest. we'll discuss--
Sign there you received it.
Pays two-hundred
and twenty a month.
Better than Chicago.
A little more risk here.
I don't know about that.
We have an orientation
at 8:00 A.M. tomorrow.
you'll receive your book
of penal codes.
and a firearm if you
don't have one.
I'm plenty armed. thank you.
Ma'am. it's been a pleasure.
Thank you for the opportunity.
How many is that?
Three.
Jacob said we need
at least twenty.
We'll get there.
It's just gonna take some time.
We don't have any time.
Cara. time is the one
thing we have in abundance.
You have it in abundance.
My family. however.
has run out.
I need to show you
something. Will.
What is that?
Schools of little fish
collecting in the shade
beneath the boat.
What's that?
Bigger fish.
Tuna. I think.
Are we in danger?
More danger than we were
five minutes ago. I mean?
I wouldn't go swimming.
Think about
it like this...
In the last six hours
this ocean has adapted
to this boat being here.
Taking advantage of it.
People think they're so smart.
People ain't that smart.
You might be.
I know I am.
I learn from my mistakes.
but I still make plenty.
Like our current situation.
Are you saying this was
likely your last tugboat ride?
No matter how this shakes out.
this was my last tugboat ride.
I refuse to be scared.
Refuse it.
I will not feel
sorry for myself.
If death is our fate
I will draw my last breath
and kiss you with it.
I swear to God.
It ain't our fate.
You're gonna need another
reason to kiss me.
Aw. This makes me smile.
You wouldn't be smiling if you
knew what I was waiting for.
I don't care what
you're waiting for
so long as you're
standing there doing it.
What are you waiting for?
See that mountain?
About two-thirds of the way up?
- See that?
- Yes. What is that?
They're cutting a road.
Up the side of a mountain?
A road to nowhere. then?
A road to somewhere.
Guess you're gonna be holding
nursing me back to health
pretty high over my head. huh?
Put it this way.
There is no more debate
about a generator.
Or a clothes-washing machine.
Pretty expensive nurse.
And you might want to lean on
your cane for this one.
- Don't say it.
- Motor car.
Oh my God. Jesus...
Suppose there's no way
I could kind of
just ease into this modern age?
Yes. of course. I'll let you
choose which one we get first.
That's mighty generous of you.
You find
any more men today?
Fewer than I'd hoped.
Well. what we can't hire.
I'll raise in a posse.
You leave all
the fighting to the agents.
I'm not going
through that again.
It's not my intention
to get shot.
Nor is it my intention
to become a widow.
So. all those thoughts
of justice in your head...
They stay there.
They're blasting a mine
right above this ranch's
main water supply.
They own the property
to the north now.
And to the south.
To squeeze what's in the middle.
And what's in the middle is us.
Justice would be a luxury.
My concern is survival.
I know.
That's why I did it.
Did what?
Don't be mad.
I did it for you.
For God sakes. Jacob.
you're a damned law man.
You know how bad this looks?
It's just like I said.
And there's a dozen
witnesses say the same.
But no proof anywhere.
You want some fucking proof?
I'll show you
some fucking proof!
And there's more proof
buried in our graveyard here
and even more proof shipped
back east and buried there.
Where's all the bodies
of all the Creighton men?
Rotting on the Wyoming border.
Well. you sure got
a lot done for a dead man.
What would you have
done different?
I would have told the sheriff.
You think you could've
kept the bank away.
along with every thief
from Laramie to Whitefish?
I understand what
the bank would've done.
And I know what the thieves
would've done if you'd died.
But you didn't.
And you still sat on this.
Now. I know what you're up to.
and I won't allow it.
Wyoming's already
had a range war.
Montana ain't
having another.
I'll arrest him in the morning.
In the meantime. everybody.
and that means you.
gives a statement
to the deputies.
Damn right. I'm mad.
Jacob.
Jacob...
How dare you give
your back to me?
After all I've given to you.
It's not even justice.
It's more petty than that.
It's vengeance you seek.
Never mind he'll be
arrested in the morning.
You'd rather put the bullet
in him yourself.
Then it's you in prison and
the ranch is lost all the same.
You think it's you
who's suffered the most?
How would you know. you were
asleep half the time.
While I bathed you and
spoon fed you like an infant.
I wiped your ass like an infant.
While I shoveled graves
between unanswered prayers.
You don't know what it
is to suffer.
Emma did. She suffered her way
into the hole I dug her.
Elizabeth knows it.
Father in the ground. family
gone. stuck in this house
like a dungeon.
Can you fathom the strength
it took for that girl
to smile again?
If there is a line
forming for vengeance.
you are at the back of it.
But we've abandoned any
desire of vengeance.
Even Jack. for you.
I wonder if your pride
can withstand the sacrifice
of showing us the same courtesy.
Son of a bitch.
Boy. come here.
I don't hear anything.
Supposed to hear
'em moving around.
Not yet.
It'll be six months or more.
You don't look pregnant.
I will be in time. trust me...
I'll be milk-cow fat
with cheeks like a beaver.
Well. if I can't hear it.
and I can't feel it
and you won't show for months.
how do you know?
Men sure know how
to make babies
but boy is that where
the knowledge stops.
I missed my monthly visitor
and then I was dizzy
and then I was nauseous.
Do you need more proof?
Well. is there more proof?
Well. there is. but that's
all I'm going to share.
Hey...
That's the past.
This is the future.
We're a year away from
making another. Jack.
Well. I was thinking this
is a pretty good
opportunity to practice.
- Practice?
- Mm-hmm.
Practice is how
we got into this.
Well. a year's a long time.
I'll forget everything.
I mean...
Look at it like this:
you can't get more pregnant.
I can't believe that's
the line that sells me.
'Cause you see
the logic in it.
Or you're just so overcome with
desire you can't think straight.
Hey!
I touched a nerve
with that one.
That's about to be
all you're touching.
Yeah?
Awful cold outside
to have that window open.
Not in that room.
Can't make two at once.
Well. it seems they are
embracing the sport of it.
We can hear ya!
You saved my life.
I know it.
I did not need to be told.
It's not vengeance .
It's preservation.
You've been to New York.
you've been to Boston.
Um-hum.
Now close your eyes
and imagine those places
if the cities weren't there.
Come on. do it.
White sands stretching
to a forest of
hickory and elm...
taller than the buildings
that stand there now.
Meadows filled with bison
and moose and bear.
and millions of salmon swimming
up the east river
to spawn. so thick.
you could walk across them.
Now think about
what's there now:
a thirteen-mile island of cement
with rivers of sewage
running underneath it
until they dump into the bay
where salmon don't dare to swim.
That's what they'll
do to this place:
dam the rivers...
flood the valleys...
cut every tree that
stands to build cities.
This paradise becomes
another concrete desert.
I'm not going to kill him
for what they done to me.
or what they done to John.
or what they're
still doing to you.
I'm going to kill them...
because the men who build cities
always send men
like Banner first.
I do it for the child
of a child I will never meet.
I do it for the land.
I do it for you.
So that when you're laid
to rest under the aspens...
no one cuts them down
and builds a city over you.
I know how much you've suffered.
And I thank you for it.
It's their turn now.
God damn it.
it's their turn now.
Spencer. Spencer.
Do you see that?
Is that the shore?
It's a ship.
See me.
Come on. see me! Come on!
See me!
They see us?
Come on. Come on.
Here we go.
Jesus. Mary. and Joseph.
I'd like to take you two
to a casino.
All right. here we are.
Just slide over here to me.
Thank you.
That's a shiny penny
that you have there. mate.
You're lucky I don't whip
this skiff around
with you still
standing on the hull.
Don't forget how
I flagged down the ship.
Teasing ya. mate.
Come on. then.
Before the sea eats
the rest of this tug.
All right. there you go.
Could I have one of those?
I suppose it's
unnecessary to point out
how lucky
you are to be alive.
You both
seem keenly aware.
I doubt you were able
to retrieve the Captain's log.
based on the condition
of your vessel.
Captain's log was the
last thing on my mind.
Yes. I suppose
it would have been.
Our port of call
is Marseilles.
What was your destination?
Tug was headed to Suez.
Beyond that. I don't know.
Our final destination
is the United States.
Quite the journey.
You could book passage
from Marseilles.
Where in the United States?
Montana.
Afraid I don't know it.
It's in the mountains.
In the middle of the country.
Your journey is only beginning
when you get to port.
You could say that.
I'd recommend the Port
of Galveston
or Port Arthur in the Gulf.
Ellis Island
is a cesspool of disease.
I hear it takes months for
an immigrant to gain entry.
I was hoping that you
could help me with that.
I have no dealings with
American immigration. sir.
You are the captain
of this ship.
I am.
These are
international waters.
They are.
Marry us.
Marriage to gain
citizenship is illegal. sir.
It's a benefit.
That's not why I'm doing it.
No.
No. I wouldn't think so.
I'd be honored.
I'll prepare the color guard.
I'd like to do it now.
If you could.
We can't make much
of a ceremony here.
but we can make something.
Putting things off
a day isn't proving conducive
to our current lifestyle.
No. I don't suppose it is.
Very well.
Don't suppose you have rings?
No rings.
When sailors pass
and we've no address
to send belongings to their
widows. they accumulate here.
See if you can find
some that fit.
Rather morbid. getting
wed with a dead sailor's ring.
Yes. I would endeavor
to replace at the first opportunity.
I don't know.
Ocean almost took us.
Now it gives us rings.
I think I'll keep mine.
They're too big.
Try this one.
Belongs to my wife.
I wear it when I'm on the sea.
I'm certain she would approve.
All right?
Your quarters. sir.
- Your essentials. my lady.
- Thank you.
Enjoy your--
Alex:
You're very still.
Odd how you can stay in
the exact same position.
no fidgeting at all.
You haven't moved in an hour.
It's quite reptilian.
Could be that I'm tired.
I think our age difference
is showing when
one good ravaging
has you knackered.
Who says I'm older?
Are you saying I look
as old as you?
Have you seen a mirror lately?
I should be exhausted as well.
But alas...
I see no sleep for me tonight.
Okay.
Surely our wedding night
warrants celebration.
Even from a curmudgeon like you.
I don't know what that means.
It is an insult. my love.
Meant for my amusement.
I know a better way
to entertain you.
Get dressed.
What are those lights?
That's Egypt.
That's the canal.
London looks like
that at night.
There's a cocoon of
light hugging the city.
No light where we're going.
Just moon and the stars.
And whatever you burn
in the fireplace.
- Why no lights?
- No electricity.
I suppose you'll tell me
there's no plumbing next.
There's no plumbing.
Fascinating the things
men fail to mention
when they're trying
to bed you.
What's your dream?
I don't dream.
Everyone has a dream.
I have plenty.
I can take some
of yours. then.
I mean it.
Tell me.
You're my husband now.
Sworn to tell me everything.
I don't remember that vow.
It's in there.
Right between your vow
to honor and obey me.
I think you got all that
shit backwards.
You weren't listening.
You must tell me everything.
honor me and obey me.
You are at risk of breaking all
three vows on our wedding night.
something else you didn't dare
mention prior to bedding me.
I'll tell you one.
I'll tell you a dream.
In my heart I know
it was wrong to take you.
And everything that happened
up to now was a sign.
A warning.
The elephant. the lions
the shipwreck.
It was all the universe
telling me to put you back.
I'm just too fucking
selfish to do it. So...
My dream is...
My dream is that
the universe is wrong.
And you're mine to keep.
The universe has
absolutely no say. whatsoever.
I am following
you wherever you go.
Whether you like
it or not.
Choose another dream.
This one's already come true.
It's far from coming true.
There is no putting me back.
We are one now.
When the sun hits your face
I am your shadow.
When it finds my back
you are mine.
I go where you go.
Even if
it's the death of me.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today